{"title": "French Language", "listOfQuestions": [{"question": "What is the French word for 'tree'?", "correctAnswer": "Arbre", "wrongAnswers": ["Mer", "Chien", "Livre"]}, {"question": "How do you say 'I want' in French?", "correctAnswer": "Je veux", "wrongAnswers": ["Bonjour", "Chat noir", "Allons à la plage"]}, {"question": "Translate the word 'house' to French.", "correctAnswer": "Maison", "wrongAnswers": ["Ami", "Eau", "Vélo"]}, {"question": "What does 'robe' mean in English?", "correctAnswer": "Dress", "wrongAnswers": ["Shirt", "Pants", "Shoes"]}, {"question": "How would you say 'good morning' in French?", "correctAnswer": "Bonjour", "wrongAnswers": ["Merci", "Au revoir", "S'il vous plaît"]}, {"question": "Translate 'blue' to French.", "correctAnswer": "Bleu", "wrongAnswers": ["Vert", "Rouge", "Jaune"]}, {"question": "What is the French word for 'table'?", "correctAnswer": "Table", "wrongAnswers": ["Fourchette", "Chaise", "Lit"]}, {"question": "How do you say 'big' in French?", "correctAnswer": "Grand / Grande", "wrongAnswers": ["Petit / Petite", "Vite / Vite", "Haut / Haute"]}, {"question": "Translate the phrase 'thank you' to French.", "correctAnswer": "Merci", "wrongAnswers": ["Bonjour", "Au revoir", "Excusez-moi"]}, {"question": "What does 'heureux' mean in English?", "correctAnswer": "Happy", "wrongAnswers": ["Sad", "Angry", "Tired"]}, {"question": "How would you say 'brother' in French?", "correctAnswer": "Frère", "wrongAnswers": ["Père", "Chien", "Ami"]}, {"question": "Translate 'to eat' to French.", "correctAnswer": "Manger", "wrongAnswers": ["Dormir", "Boire", "Étudier"]}, {"question": "What is the French word for 'dance'?", "correctAnswer": "Danse", "wrongAnswers": ["Musique", "Film", "Livre"]}, {"question": "How do you say 'green' in French?", "correctAnswer": "Verte", "wrongAnswers": ["Rouge", "Bleue", "Jaune"]}, {"question": "Translate the word 'cat' to French.", "correctAnswer": "Chat", "wrongAnswers": ["Chien", "Oiseau", "Poisson"]}, {"question": "What does 'fleur' mean in English?", "correctAnswer": "Flower", "wrongAnswers": ["Tree", "River", "Mountain"]}, {"question": "How would you say 'to run' in French?", "correctAnswer": "Courir", "wrongAnswers": ["Cuisiner", "Nager", "Dormir"]}, {"question": "Translate 'hat' to French.", "correctAnswer": "Chapeau", "wrongAnswers": ["Chaussures", "Pantalons", "Chemise"]}, {"question": "What is the French word for 'school'?", "correctAnswer": "École", "wrongAnswers": ["Maison", "Travail", "Parc"]}, {"question": "Translate the phrase 'good night' to French.", "correctAnswer": "Bonne nuit", "wrongAnswers": ["Bonjour", "Merci", "Au revoir"]}]}
